Guide to the Arnold Isenberg Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Arnold Isenberg papers
1938-1963
SC1148
Isenberg, Arnold
6 Linear feet
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Access Terms
Camper, Fred
Collection Contents
- Papers
  - Arnold (Poetry Collection), 1949-1957 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Arnold, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Unlabeled Photos, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Professor for Motherhood Dept of Philosophy, 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Arnold, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - A.I., 1956 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Pages 1803-1885, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Pages 1886-1939, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Pages 2000-2071, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Pages 2072-2217, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Pages 2218-2268, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Pages 2269-2326, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Pages 2327-2525, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Pages 2525-2647, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Pages 2648-2807, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Pages 2808-2854, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Pages 2855-2869, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Pages 2928-3039, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Pages 3040-3204, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Pages 3205-3206, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Pages 3391-3420, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Pages 3500-3590, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Pages 3591-3739, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Pages 3740-3867, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Pages 3869-3999, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Pages 4000-4153, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Pages 4154-4342, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Pages 4342-4360, undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Pages 4361-4436, undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Pages 4437-4556, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Pages 4557-4665, undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Assorted Philosophy Journals, 1956-1963 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - jms (Poetry Collection), 1955 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - jms Assorted Poetry, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - jms Assorted Poetry, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - jms Assorted Poetry, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Pages 7-41, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Pages 42-133, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Pages 133-246, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Pages 247-315, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Pages 316-471, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Pages 472-941, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Pages 942-1249, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Pages 1251-1516, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Pages 1517-1807 (End of Roll), undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Pages 1808-2042, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Pages 2043-2071, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Pages 2072-2217, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Arnold's Papers Pages 1-471, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Unnumbered, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Pages 1-171, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Assorted Notes, Postcards, Photos, Stenographer's Notebook, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Pages 1-1714 (copy), undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Logic: Journals of Symbolic Logic and Notes, 1938-1953 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - "Does Quality Order Rest Upon A Mistake?", undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - "Proposed Experiments on Measurement of Utility", undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Pages 1-34 Shirley C. Soman, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Pages 35-80, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Pages 81-120, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Pages 121-150, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Pages 151-213, undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Pages 214-500, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Pages 501-655, undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Pages 656-789, undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Pages 790-914, undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Pages 915-1128, undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Pages 1129-1142, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Pages 1143-1164, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Pages 1165-1393, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Pages 1394-1418, undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Pages 1420-1493, undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Pages 1494-1548, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Pages 1549-1561, undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Pages 1562-1712, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Pages 1713-1802, undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - The Journal of Philosophy Vol. L, No. 15, 1953 July 16 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - The Journal of Philosophy Vol. XLII, No. 19, 1945 Sept. 13 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - The Journal of Philosophy Vol. LII, No. 17, 1955 Aug. 18 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - The Journal of Philosophy Vol. LIII, No. 18, 1956 Aug. 30 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - The Journal of Philosophy Vol. LV, No. 21, 1958 Oct. 9 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Accent, 1959 Autumn (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - The Journal of Philosophy Vol. LIII, No. 14, 1956 July 5 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - The Journal of Philosophy Vol. LII, No. 7, 1955 March 31 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - The Journal of Philosophy Vol. LIII, No. 6, 1956 March 15 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - The Journal of Philosophy Vol. LIII, No. 9, 1956 April 26 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - The Journal of Philosophy Vol. LIII, No. 12, 1956 June 7 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - The Journal of Philosophy Vol. LII. No. 21, 1955 Oct. 13 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Philosophical Studies Vol. 1, No. 1, 1950 Jan. (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - The Journal of Philosophy Vol. LIII. No. 17, 1956 Aug.16 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - The Journal of Philosophy Vol. LI. No. 13, 1954 June 24 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Poetry and Ethics Exam Book and Various Essays, circa 1963 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Arnold Isenberg Info, Undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - "The Present Situation in the Aesthetics of Poetry", Undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - "The Aesthetic Judgement is Singular", Undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Pages 2524-2647, Undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - "Please Island" Poem, Undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Pages 1420-1493, Undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Art and Wish "To The Reader", Undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - 9 Pages of Hand Notes, Undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - "Program Music" and "Musics and Ideas", Undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - "Mystery", Undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Pages 2-32 and Page 1943 (2 copies), Undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Pages 2272-2297, Undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Pages 2298-4665, Undated (Box 4, Folder 14)